foreign
weapon systems are buzzing did that
sting Taking Flight I'm the queen bee
you hear me baby hold together remember
me mediocre you're going to get a
parking ticket that was your last
warning Diva reporting in
flooring it burning rubber cool it get
bent pop the clutch and let's go popped
up and ready to kill no sweat right oh
firing up I'm cooking hey I'm no ankle
biter I'm cruising for a bruising you
ordered a knuckle sandwich
far out time to split cutting out hey
Daddio we got this made in the shade
oh you shouldn't have I'm not scared oh
I'm ready to initiate self-destruct
sequence ultimate ready meta activated
hit you with that
boo
I play to win and I always do
that's just who I am
someone has to say the world it might as
well be me
GG
s
[Music]
slicer's incoming slicer incoming enemy
teleporter located try and keep up here
no problem
you're welcome time to save the world
game on yes
Genji I heard you used to have all the
high scores here
the destruction caused by the omnics
here
it reminds me of home let's shoot for a
new high score
you remind me of someone you're so
serious though taeyeon he's great isn't
he a giant gorilla just like in those
old video games
Ready Player One all systems operational
Diva ready for combat may I love reading
your Journal I'm so jealous you get to
go to all those places
of course here you go
love diva
blizzard games that's so old school oh
only if I could get yours too I love
your new album
16-bit hero oh come on Anna I bet you
got up to all sorts of trouble when you
were my age I'm going to own all these
noobs alright game face on are you sure
life isn't a game Soldier 76 my mechanic
taeyeon does a great job on it I bet
he'd love to meet you
who are you calling a child
this is my kind of City Lights Camera
Action I can't wait to get into the
fight hey Sombra I hear you're a master
of unlocking oh after this match is over
right now it's time to get serious
oh I can't stand you hackers you give
those of us with skill a bad name I hope
this doesn't take too long I have a show
to put on my New Year's resolution catch
up on all the games I need to play well
if you want to give me some upgrades I'm
all ears no one's beating my high scores
well
they flew me to the Moon
size isn't everything I am not the
Easter Bunny think you can keep up with
me
hey hands off they've stolen our flag
they have our flag get it back
no in three two one three two one lol
Diva one bad guy zero don't tell Tana
you got this reset and regroup I'm not
giving up
am I getting stream sniped
with only a warm-up they're counting on
me
we all need help sometimes
Saint by the rabbit Diva to the rescue
as always we need to group up to
continue get on the objective with me
come to the objective hey team up here
[Music]
time to eliminate the objective the
objective has been taken out roll for
need objective down
[Laughter]
oh
enemy Detonator over here is this easy
mode
hostile's on the point are they for real
they're taking our Point Let's light up
that kill feed hey that's my objective
fight's not over yet all we have to do
is win this round
setback but we can still win this
not feeling right I've been debuffed now
that's DPS
no problem
don't call me baby
I'm on fire what else is new
Customs really hot your carry is here
now or never stop them and we win it's
their last push let's crush them yeah
enemy spotted let's wipe them out we're
almost out of time don't let up now I'm
on offense behind you no problem I'm low
Health pocket me need healing I need
healing heels please warm up everyone we
must gather together before venturing
forth
ah
[Music]
get ready I'm with you I get the feeling
you're not taking me seriously I'm
number one
Gigi game on let's make up this party
miss me Diva back in Action
we have a teammate down no one to steal
my Spotlight where'd everyone go I'm a
professional
you can't be serious
oh
oh move that robot
push the robot no hex required
scoreboard go they're catching up to us
stop them don't let them catch up we
can't let them take the lead attack the
objective come on we have to catch up
they have the lead stop them oh we lost
the lead it's our turn let's push
forward let's start to push start
pushing the barricade
happy Halloween hey stick with the robot
we got the robot go go go rally near the
robot and keep pushing why stop that
glorious be notorious
oh who am I going to go with now it's
salty and spicy and garlicky it's yummy
fried too this city always smells like
melted butter and rats I bet you're a
pro at bowling I have to introduce you
to Overlord he's the best pilot I know
nah hey
who took my Nano Cola why stop at making
it here I'm thinking more Global I'm the
best that's all you need to know
you didn't
right it's probably risky for us to talk
at all
sometimes but I have so much to do can't
they get anything done without us let me
take you shopping in Seoul I'll find you
all the cutest stuff I should introduce
you to taeyeon he takes care of my Mac
when I'm back home uh I don't know I
heard your inventions take five minutes
to boot up if they destroy any of my
favorite mud chips I'm coming for them
look at this team we're gonna do great
why don't you give them a try maybe then
you'd frown less a Mecca road trip would
be ton of fun oh that's what it is not
bad I'll stop you even with your hacks I
get it everyone's scared to take on the
best player in the world don't worry no
one will touch a feather on ganny's head
while Hana song is here
it sounds better when I say it Genji
let's go to the arcade after this
can you be good at shooting in real life
but so bad in games I heard you're a
good dancer you should try to beat my
high score and dance floor
Someday I'm gonna finally travel the
world got any tips let's sneak in a trip
to the beach after this I won't tell if
you don't that's just the way I like it
uh what
the paparazzi better not get in my way
oh finally a balanced 1v1
whoa that gun must do a ton of DPS cute
hook what's that you're hiding so far in
the back line I could barely hear you
it's nice being on home turf uh I'm way
cooler than you
so don't take it personally when I get
the most kills okay
um no all systems fired up and ready to
engage
the bad guys won't know what hit him why
so serious Reinhardt you're supposed to
be the fun one
can jump over Big Ben no problem oh no
the tall one with the little hat you
should visit me in Korea Lina uh didn't
you lose an entire jet once I saw you on
a wanted poster with a cute guy there's
something off about your Vibe yeah he
hey
it's Lonely at the Top how can you
experiment on those cute little rabbits
it's funny Soldier 76 said the same
thing your crazy strong zarya how many
of me could you lift stick together let
me take the hits wait for real you don't
look so good maybe you should sit this
one out and leave the kills to me you
just wanted to drink it yourself
now I'm hungry
he prepped all night for this Mission
well maybe I gained a little too
I'll show you true Hospitality career
style we should get ganymy to scout for
us we got this go robot go keep pushing
for the win
we have the lead our teammate needs to
be revived our Squad mates down help
them up
blah enjoy that kill cam
oh played haha my ultimate is charging
focus our defense on the objective now
no way or 14-sided prepare to engage get
dunked on oh bad positioning
squished that was the wrong place to
stand over there I'll watch here Diva
scoping here I'll scout out here
level up wow the few is amazing
fully operational healed up
looks like I'm gonna have to carry don't
worry I've got this move the payload the
enemy is above us they're attacking from
the front enemy contact in front of us
they're below us they're above us
they're coming from behind watch the
left left side right side watch the
right the enemy is below us enemy
contact at 12 o'clock the enemy is
behind us Nerf this
SmackDown
to the hand
ouch
don't mess with me pistol in the face
knocked down take this returning the
flag Flags going back to base
we've got this don't let up now looks
like another Victory just a little
longer I know my kdr I'm on defense come
on
oh
okay
okay no
understood death I read you copy that
Roger okay got it on the objective and
ready for action Mecca securing the
point if they want this point they'll
have to go through me fall back now's
our chance press the attack
send it we need a Healer I could use
some armor I need armor
haven't had enough
ah no fair back for more they want a
rematch bring it group up here group up
join me let's group up group up with me
come on they're not even trying
um I think you mean bomb shatter massive
bomb shatter can volskaya's mechs do
that
oh
[Music]
heads up watch out ping ping ping
oh
no my ultimate is almost ready
[Laughter]
this is our win fight fight fight
we're almost there don't choke hold out
and we cinch this win oh
I've got everything under control defend
our flag cover our flag smash through
that door we need to clear the path
clear the path forward oh yeah
take cover take out the target uh oh I
dropped it I dropped it oh what did I
get oh for me no Trooper spotted no
Troopers spotted
huh
nice try love Diva HP Max
ah you must like me thanks yeah pocket
healer cap the flag Diva with the score
attack the objective let's capture the
objective come on this way take the
enemy flag capture the flag find the
teleporter our numbers are low careful
we're outnumbered
oh
thanks
thank you
[Music]
booting up new Mech new me come here
Toki initializing systems calling in the
big guns
enemy turret ahead turkey mobilizing my
time to shine
see you at the Finish Line give me that
this one's for me
oh my I got it I'm on the next level new
record I'm just getting started now
they're just feeding oh how's my KD him
coming
save that for the Hall of Fame that's a
star performance clear the area
stop the payload oh come on we can push
the payload farther than that hello the
payload's not moving push the payload
win the fight I've got this let's do it
no sweat Press Start get me back in the
fight I'm very hurt over here
help me up I'm not done yet revive me
I'm seriously injured Diva logging on
Diva online hiya
[Music]
go forward activating self-destruct
sequence
I'm gonna mess you up
let's go
not bad
glad you're on my team wow you're
popping off Nice Shot
you've been holding back on me and yes
My ultimate is charged Ready Player Two
My ultimate is ready let's do this
perfect weather for a hot dog where's my
backup where is everyone it's quiet is
everyone AFK enemy Shield generator
destroyed I'll see you at the finish
line
stop their push come on stop the robot I
could use some Shields I need Shields
ready flying high engaging thrusters
diving in mobilizing
speeding up last round this is where it
counts this is it come on team here
comes a new Challenger time to go let's
move defend the objective
foreign
let's finish this right now we've got
this one more round and we win the Dream
Team I'm the dream you're the team enemy
teleporter destroyed ah there they are
thanks for the love oh
oh
get up I still need your help you and me
we've got this don't rage quit on me
come on the fight's not over yet we need
you in this team fight focus our attacks
on the objective destroy the objective
heads up enemy Bastion someone stealth
over here enemy detected I don't feel
the attraction time out cowboy
boring nice try love don't think so
looks like I consume the dragon excuse
you oops was that your best hold your
fire you're not in the forecast
brain freeze try try try again hey no
littering look at you now look at me bye
bye bye
nothing to see here sniper don't get
caught get the flag back recover our
flag
someone else take the flag dropped the
flag the best things in life come in
small packages everyone to the objective
move to the objective this is our last
chance let's win this thing time's
almost up and we need more kills we
don't have much longer time to clutch
this protect the objective defend the
objective oh me pure skill
ah go next we're making progress keep
going enemy objective is damaged come on
you can do it and they say I waste time
come on we have a mission to finish
someone want to get that trust me
pressing buttons isn't that hard winky
face
all out for the count this game is so
free
oh or kill I'm out pilot disengaging
talkie compromised BRB gotta bail
damn it
oh come on let's not let that happen
again
um you need aim training
too spicy for you
enemy down
who invited the Brookie are you even
trying crushed hard countered it's a
skill issue
I thought ninjas had good reaction time
Target eliminated that one's for my fans
check you're dead
this rabbit fights back
wow cringe
hey they have a teleporter
enemy spotted enemy here
found an enemy pushing the payload
where's my team payload rolling out
payload mobilized let's get this win
just push a little more we're almost
there we're so close to winning come on
the lead's almost ours yeah oh they're
moving the payload enemies on the
payload let's get them they're pushing
the payload stop them clear those noobs
off the payload sorry about that
sorry sorry
enemy turrets not gonna bother us
anymore enemy turret destroyed I'm right
here I'm over here
[Music]
the bear keeps moving let's stop them
they're pushing ahead
stop them from pushing the barricade I'm
going in one year older one year wiser
flag is in my possession I have the flag
touch our flag quick
someone pick up our flag bang the object
is close let's go get to the Waypoint
come on let's get to the objective last
one to the objective buys ice cream
after the mission
found their Shield generator that
objective is going down
shouldn't take much more get out of
there power up now that's teamwork
weapons optimized power up
damage buff uh yeah now we're talking
weapon systems overloaded
[Music]
no
huge rest one up
Game Changer they have a shield
generator
initiating defense Matrix forward
barrier activated neutralizing
projectiles
nothing gets past me
how do you like that
good luck climbing from down there
you're not on my level
s wow you fell far let's move the
objective together let's keep the
objective moving final push show them up
last push Make It Count
thick with the robot and we win last
chance stay with the robot I could use a
hand I need help that blew up in your
face monkey monkey monkey oh
we got him that was like a boss battle
there's an Eradicator what the they have
the robot they stole the robot from us
get it back let's take the robot back on
my way OMW set up here
AFK I give everything to protect my home
so don't trifle with me
oops tunnel vision apology accepted